geminisoundsradio.com 2014-10-12

# Privacy Policy | Gemini Sounds Radio- The People's Station Broadcasting Worldwide 24/7 Internet Radio

The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a user of Gemini Sounds Radio and our Internet radio broadcasts, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you use our service, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information.

In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers, frequency and domains of visitors to Gemini Sounds Radio and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate to analyze trends and statistics. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our Gemini Sounds Radio partners about how our visitors, collectively, use geminisoundsradio.com. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well.

What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service, like the Gemini Sounds Radiomessage boards, We will need certain information -- such as name, Internet address, user ID or member name, type of computer, in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional features and services about which you might be interested. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to respond or not.

Information About You

Cookies and How We Use Them

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Gemini Sounds Radio or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. But as we mention above, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of Gemini Sounds Radio

Disclosure

Children's Online Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy for Gemini Sounds Radio, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

Gemini Sounds Radio Privacy Policy Changes

OUR PRIVACY POLICY

A cookie is a small file stored on your computer by a Web site to give you a unique ID. Cookies help make it easier for you to use our site, and they help us provide you with the information you need - when and where you need it. Cookies provided by our Web site do not contain any credit card or personal information, and we do not use cookies to personally identify anonymous site visitors.

Gemini Sounds Radio are committed to the preservation of online privacy for all of its Web site visitors, including children. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you provide personal information at Gemini Sounds Radio. you are representing that you are an adult. If you are a child under the age of 13, you must ask your parent or guardian to assist you in using Gemini Sounds Radio.
